# Do Dinh Anh

Web Developer

Gender: Male

Phone: +84 987.196.695

Email: dinhanhdo95@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

I'm Do Dinh Anh, a web developer with over 3 years of experience in JavaScript technologies, with good knowledge of UI, UX, Object-Oriented and Design Patterns.

Learning new languages and technologies is what I'm really keen on. I'm considered a teamplayer because I prefer to discuss innovative ideas with others and tend to work well within the group.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Programming Languages:
  - JavaScript, NodeJS, C#.NET
  - HTML5, CSS3
- Frameworks/ Platforms:
  - ReactJS, VueJS, ExpressJS
  - Webpack, Gulp, Babel
  - ES6, Typescript
  - Javascript SDK, PWA, RESTful API
  - Sass, Twitter Bootstrap
  - ASP.NET MVC, Web API
  - Docker
- Database Management Systems:
  - MS SQL Server, MySQL
- Others:
  - Good understanding of OOP methodologies
  - Experience with Agile and Scrum development process
  - Others.

# **Working Experiences**

# Savvycom 09/2019 - Present

# **Web Developer**

Superfanz

- **Project Description**: A social platform content creator, is the next level online fan club for global creators across 10 countries and their most hardcore fans aka super fans, enables super fans easiest way to pay their favorite musician, blogger, fashionista, Youtubers, Foodie and so much more.

- Version Control:
  - Git, SVN
- Foreign Languages:

## English:

- Good reading/writing
- Fair verbal communication
- Soft Skills:
  - Time management
  - Problem solving
  - Teamwork

- **Team Size**: 20
- Responsibilities:

Collaborate with product team members to implement new feature developments.

Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy which increased mobile traffic by 15%. Integrate social media logins, payment processors and other services.

 Technologies: VueJS, NuxtJS, Webpack, Sass, Vuetify, PWA, NodeJS, NestJS

# NTQ Solution 05/2018 – 09/2019

#### **Web Developer**

Serimu Jvideos

- Project Description: An enhanced experience video system. It attracts creators and makers to join the system so that they can improve, contribute to it and then viewers can enjoy and wind down whenever they want.
- Team Size: 22Responsibilities:

Communicate with customers and teammates to clarify requirements.

Develop key modules of the system that saved around 20% of the development time of other functionalities.

- Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, Webpack, Sass, Ant Design, PWA

## M-Solutions ARMS

- Project Description: Dealing with the client side of a firing alarm system so that the customer can completely be in control of problems accurately.
- Team Size: 8
- Responsibilities:

Communicate with customers and teammates to report daily works Build up features and implement unit tests based on requirements.

- Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, Saga, ImmutableJS, Reselect, Jest

# Pronexus-Works

- Project Description: Develop a local application, it's one of a system lies in a huge ecosystem of the organization that is taking up 60% of finance in the Japanese market and manages tons of documents and links related to that field.
- Team Size: 7
- Responsibilities:

Analyze specifications and recommend the best solutions to the customer

Build up features and implement unit tests based on requirements

Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, Redux Thunk, Reselect, Jest

# PowerGate Software 06/2017 - 04/2018

## **Junior Developer**

OneIT Mobile

- Project Description: Develop a mobile management system. To better assist customers that can quickly give options and select suitable mobile phones conveniently.
- **Team Size**: 5
- Responsibilities:

Communicate with customers to get clear requirements Compose APIs and evolve modules of the system

- **Technologies:** Angular 2, HTML5, CSS3, ASP.NET Web API, Entity Framework, MS SQL Server

# OneIT CoventryCRM

- Project Description: A meeting management application supports people to book their customer's appointments with anyone whenever they want, from wherever you are.
- **Team Size**: 6
- Responsibilities:

Communicate with customers and teammates to get clear requirements.

Develop the frameworks and modules of the system.

Technologies: Angular 2, Webpack, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 3

# **Education and Qualification**

• 2013 – 2017

Certification: Engineering

- Learning in: Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology, Vietnam

Specialized in: Information Technology

2018 – 2019

- Certification: Agile Developers

Learning in: Agile Academy, VietnamSpecialized in: Information Technology